

# **My Contact**

mailvishwadeephere@gmail.com

**(** +91 7814092325

https://vishwadeep-s.netlify.app/

#### **Skills**

- React
- Gatsby
- MUI
- Tailwind
- GSAP
- GraphQL
- Vue
- NodeJS
- NestJS
- ExpressPostgreSQL
- MongoDB
- Mongobb
- CosmosDB

- Netlify Functions
- Azure DevOps
- Azure Blob Storage
- Docker
- Kubernetics
- Google Maps API
- Google Images
- API Keyvault
- Github
- Autho
- Keycloak
- Azure Functions

# Vishwadeep Singh

# Full Stack Developer

#### **About Me**

I believe that there is always a room for improvements regardless of one's level of expertise. These improvements can only be brought by trying new things and making mistakes while doing it. Learning from mistakes and having a positive attitude is the key to growth. I am also a technology believer and I believe that a better place for everyone can be achieved with advancements in tech.

# **Professional Experience**

#### SleekSky | Software Development Engineer

08/2022 - CURRENT

- I worked with NestJS, React, Express, Azure, Keycloak and tools around them while at SleekSky.
- I am responsible for building robust backend and frontend using react, node, nest.js and technologies around it.
- While at Sleeksky, I worked on a CMS, adding payment feature and a json visual form editor; and on a University-Hospital Student placement management application.

#### FlockAlong | Web Developer

12/2020 - 08/2022

- I worked with Gatsby, Nodejs, Netlify Functions, C#, Auth0, Google Maps, Algolia, Cypress while at FlockAlong.
- I was responsible for developing Gatsby based Front-End which served as a platform for customers to create, join and manage trips.
- Developed and deployed Back-End on Azure to facilitate the front-end. Implemented Algolia search engine and automated data updating to Algolia servers

#### KhaoBao | Operations Manager

12/2020 - 08/2022

- I was responsible for development of Android Apps Customer Side and Delivery Guy app.
- In parallel I was handling day to day operations including signing new restaurants, improving customer experience and launching new services.
- Completed 40k successful orders over a period of more than 14 months.

## **Education**

## Languages

English, Hindi